<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backrooms on ACG资源导航站</title><link>https://v2daospace.github.io/tags/backrooms/</link><description>Recent content in Backrooms on ACG资源导航站</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://v2daospace.github.io/tags/backrooms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>【3D/生肉/无码】cumrooms [v0.6]</title><link>https://v2daospace.github.io/posts/44wk4wo48k8wck0h/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://v2daospace.github.io/posts/44wk4wo48k8wck0h/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="本页为收录内容-点击下方按钮跳转查看内容详情"&gt;本页为收录内容 点击下方按钮跳转查看内容详情&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.v2dao.com/contents/%E3%80%903d-%E7%94%9F%E8%82%89-%E6%97%A0%E7%A0%81%E3%80%91cumrooms-v0-6" style="color: #fff; background: #e74c3c; padding: 14px 36px; border-radius: 8px; font-size: 1.3em; font-weight: bold; text-decoration: none; box-shadow: 0 4px 16px rgba(0,0,0,0.15); display: inline-block;"&gt;前往查看详情&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="简介"&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024/4/30 链接已补
制作组：MOON LOOM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORY
If you’re not careful and you noclip out of reality in the wrong areas, you’ll end up in the Backrooms, where it’s nothing but the stink of old moist carpet, the madness of mono-yellow, the endless background noise of fluorescent lights at maximum hum-buzz, and approximately six hundred million square miles of randomly segmented empty rooms to be trapped in.
If you are one of the unfortunate few who do end up here, beware that there is no such thing as certainty, and you may not even be in the Backrooms you thought you were. If your (mis)fortune has brought you into the Cumrooms, well, best to stay vigilant.
Don’t be swayed by the strange yet sexy entities here; your cock and balls won’t survive the trip.
But if you are brave, stupid, or just generally horny, then maybe this isn’t such a bad way to go out…
GAMEPLAY
Delve into the backrooms from your average office job. You will then find yourself evading a very sexy beast, solving puzzles, and exploring the famous halls of the backrooms! Your main objective is to find the hatch and do everything in your power to get back to the surface.
After a successful attempt at escaping, you will get rewarded with money, which can be used to buy new items.
There are many items with a wide variety of uses, and some have a very special power.
There are 3 difficulty levels, each one harder but more rewarding than the one before.
After you get on your feet and buy all of the items you need to effectively survive, you can buy the horny spray and start a whole new world of horny adventures!
游戏截图&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>